Victor Ivanov

Multidisciplinary designer and developer.

V-os.ca Montreal, Qc - Tokyo, Japan victor.ivanov.design@gmail.com (514) 621-9322

I'm Victor. I write code, create graphics/illustrations, play and produce music, build worlds, and many other things in-between. My experience with varied media allows me to communicate effectively with different specialists, as well as exercise a high degree of control and understanding of the overarching design and vision of a project. My generalist approach equally helps me acquire and master new skills at a very fast pace, making me an effecient creator at any level of specialty.

My website, v-os.ca, includes more information about me, and documentation of my projects.

Experience

Game Workshop Technical Lead - Abtec

Instructor for game design and development workshop. Jun 2018 - Sep 2018, Honolulu Hawaii

Designer and Artist - Ubisoft Game Lab Competition

Unity game and level design, asset modeling and texturing. Jan 2018 - Apr 2018, Montreal

Research Assistant - Obx Labs

HTC Vive, iOS, Hololens, and Unity development. Jan 2017 - Apr 2017, Jan 2018 - Jun 2018, Montreal

Teaching Assistant-Concordia University

CART253 - Creative computation class. Sep 2017 - Dec 2017, Montreal

Game Design Teacher - Dawson College

Teacher for accelerated game design camp. Jun 2017 - Aug 2017, Montreal

Web Designer - Arthem Co.

Client requirements, UI, and interaction design. Mar 2016 - Oct 2016, Montreal

Education

Computation Arts - Bachelors of Fine Arts

Golf Classic Scholarship Concordia University, 2016 - Present

SILS - School of International Liberal Studies

Japanese, Architecture, Media Design Waseda University, 2018 - Present

Interactive Media Arts - First Class Honors DEC

Honor Roll, 2015-2016 Dawson College, 2015 - 2016

Languages

English, French, Bulgarian, Spanish, Japanese

Skills

Design

Audio / Visual Digital Media Production Web / Game / Application Programming Game / Software / Experience Design

Visual

Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom, Photography Premiere, Sony Vegas, After Effects, Filming, Editing Blender, Cinema4D, Terragen, ZBrush, Substance

Audio

Ableton Live, FL Studio, Logic Pro, MaxMSP Sound Synthesis, Recording, Mixing and Production Keyboard, Guitar

Code

HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript, Ruby, NodeJS, mySQL Unity3D, Unreal Engine 4 C#, Java, Processing, PureData, Arduino

Projects

Purity | v-os.ca/purity

Web-based wiki engine with API, markup language, and content management system, made using PHP.

Relay | v-os.ca/relay

Asymmetric, multiplayer, geolocative hacking game made using NodeJS.

Log | log.v-os.ca

Daily log time-tracker and data visualization program made using Ruby, MySQL, and PHP.

The Cosmic Affliction | v-os.ca/the cosmic affliction

Multi-genre electronic album, made primarily using sound synthesis, featuring guitar, piano, and vocals.

DotCycle | v-os.ca/dotcycle

Atmospherics-oriented, narrative-centric game, made using Unity and Blender.